RG 079:001, Department of Environmental Protection: Central Office
Connecticut State Library
- Series 8. Hearings, 1973-1984; 1988-024
  - Carbon Copies, 1979 (Box 14-1)
    - Hearings, 1979 (Box 14-1)
      - Harry’s Marine, 1978 June 8 (Box 14-2)
      - Harry’s Marine O/A, 1978 December 24 (Box 14-2)
      - wc- HENDEL INVESTORS (Box 14-2)
      - Honey Comb Association (Box 14-2)
      - Honey Comb Association- Oral Arguments (Box 14-2)
      - Jade Homes, Inc. (Box 14-3)
      - Johnstone Company, 1978 July 26 (Box 14-3)
      - Juliano, Jerry (Box 14-3)
      - Juliano, Jerry (Box 14-3)
      - Juliano, Jerry (Box 14-3)
      - Kahn, Morton B. (Box 14-3)
      - Kopnicky (Horizon Hgts) (Box 14-3)
      - Lasker, Marvin (Box 14-3)
      - Loveland (Box 14-3)
      - Low Flow Regs (Box 14-3)
      - M+M Development (Box 14-3)
      - Macchi Engineers (Dept. of Public Works) (Box 14-3)
      - Mason Island Marina (Box 14-3)
      - Mason Island Marina, 1978 March 30 (Box 14-3)
      - Mason Island Marina Oral Arguments (Box 14-3)
      - Milford, 1978 June 20 (Box 14-3)
      - Milford Engineering Association (Box 14-3)
      - Milford - Oral Arguments (Box 14-3)
      - Milford Wetlands Delineation (Box 14-3)
      - Muscolino, 1978 January 13 (Box 14-3)
      - Muscolino - Oral Argument (Box 14-3)
      - Mystic Seaport (Box 14-3)
      - New Haven Terminal, 1978 September 20 (Box 14-3)
      - New Haven Terminal, 1978 September 20 (Box 14-3)
      - New London Redevelopment Agency, 1978 April 8 (Box 14-3)
      - New London, 1977 December 21 (Box 14-3)
      - New London (Rogovin), 1978 September 7 (Box 14-3)
      - Nivers, Mrs. Daniel, 1978 June 27 (Box 14-3)
      - Norwalk (BOE) (Box 14-3)
      - Norwalk, City of, 1978 August 29 (Box 14-3)
      - Oppel, Clarence W. (Box 14-3)
      - Pleasant View (ESM Association), 1978 March 22 (Box 14-3)
      - Pleasant View (ESM Association), 1978 March 28 (Box 14-3)
      - Ratick, Elayne (Box 14-3)
      - Ratick, Oral Arguments (Box 14-3)
      - Renz, Ronald R. (Box 14-3)
      - Rocky Neck Hearing (Box 14-4)
      - Rocky Neck (Box 14-4)
      - Rocky Neck, 1978 September 28 (Box 14-4)
      - J.M. Rosa (Box 14-4)
      - Route 25-DOT, 1978 April 24 (Box 14-4)
      - Route 25- O/A, 1978 September 8 (Box 14-4)
      - Route 72 Plainville, 1978 July 24-25 (Box 14-4)
      - Sachem’s Head Yacht Club, Inc. Guilford, 1978 May 25 (Box 14-4)
      - Second, Peter (Box 14-4)
      - Shell Beach, E. Haven (Box 14-4)
      - Shell Beach, E. Haven, 1978 September 13 (Box 14-4)
      - Simpson, Arthur F., 1978 March 21 (Box 14-4)
      - Stratford, Town of (Box 14-4)
      - Leo Tarius Corporation (Box 14-4)
      - Tokeneke Club (Box 14-4)
      - Torrington, 1978 February 22 (Box 14-4)
      - Townsend (Box 14-4)
      - Trefz, Christian, 1978 August 23 (Box 14-4)
      - Wallingford, 1978 February 21 (Box 14-4)
      - Wargo (Box 14-4)
      - Warso, William (Oral Argument) (Box 14-4)
      - Willington, 1977 December 15 (Box 14-4)
      - William, H. Wilson 78 (Box 14-4)
      - UCONN Post Office (Box 14-4)
      - Zeigler (Old Saybrook) (Box 14-4)
- Series 9. Tri-State Regional Planning Commission, 1977-1978; 1988-024 (part)
  - Minutes and special reports, 1977-1978 (Box 5-1 - 5-2)
    The Tri-State Regional Planning Commission is the official metropolitan planning organization for the interstate urban region of Connecticut, New Jersey and New York.
    Unarranged.
- Series 10. Internal Affairs, 1973-1975; 1988-027 (part)
  - Assistant Commissioner Kenneth Wood, Jr., 1973-1975
    - Council of State Governments Regional Conference Committee on Environment (Box 17-1)
    - General Correspondence (Box 17-1)
    - Personnel (Box 17-1)
    - Personnel (resumes) (Box 17-1)
    - Soil and Water (Box 17-1)
    - Soil and Water Conservation District (Box 17-1)
    - Soil and Water Conservation (Box 17-1)
    - Photographs (Box 17-1)
    - Inland Wetlands (Box 17-2)
    - Move Plan (leased areas) (Box 17-2)
    - Move Plan (State Office Building) (Box 17-2)
    - Move Plan (Space-Middletown) (Box 17-2)
    - Solid Waste, 1971 December - 1972 December (Box 17-2)
    - Talcott Mountain and Tower (Box 17-2)
    - Telephone Numbers (Box 17-2)
    - Vehicle Identification-DEP (Box 17-2)
    - University of Connecticut (Box 17-2)
    - V-W (Box 17-2)
    - Water Companies (Box 17-2)
    - X-Y-Z (Box 17-2)
    - Move Plan (Personnel and Equipment Information) (Box 17-2)
    - Air Compliance (Box 17-2)
    - Air Pollution (Box 17-3)
    - Aerial Spraying (Box 17-3)
    - Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service (Box 17-3)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 17-3)
    - Bankers Pollution Code (Box 17-3)
    - Boating (Box 17-3)
    - Bond Funds (Box 17-3)
    - Boat “Adlib”-Lund, Mark (Dr.) (Box 17-3)
    - Bridgeport Airport I.L.S. Marsh (Box 17-3)
    - B-C (Box 17-3)
    - Camping (State Parks) (Box 17-3)
    - Citizen Complaints (Box 17-3)
    - Civil Actions (Box 17-3)
    - Compliance (Box 17-3)
    - D (Box 17-3)
    - Data Services Center-Environmental (Box 17-3)
    - E (Box 17-3)
    - Eagleville Dam Project (Box 17-3)
    - Eastern Connecticut Resource Conservation (Box 17-3)
    - Eastern Connecticut Resource Conservation and Development Project (Box 17-3)
    - Environmental Action Fund (Box 17-3)
    - Environmental Defense Fund (Box 17-3)
    - Environmental Impact-Housing Project (Groton) (Box 17-3)
    - Environmental Policy Act (State) (Box 17-3)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (Boston) (Box 17-3)
    - F-G (Box 17-3)
    - Great Creek, Milford (Box 17-3)
    - H (Box 17-3)
    - KCCB-Background Information (Box 17-3)
    - King’s Mark Resource Conservation (Box 17-3)
    - L (Box 17-3)
    - Land Acquisition and Land Development (Box 17-3)
    - Legislative Bills-Environmental (Passed and/or Favored) (Box 17-3)
    - Lufkin, Dan W.-Correspondence and memos (Box 17-3)
    - M (Box 17-3)
    - Memorandum (Internal) (Box 17-3)
    - National Association of State Environmental Protection Agencies (Box 17-3)
    - New Haven Water Company (Hamden Land) (Box 17-3)
    - New Haven Water Company (Town of Orange) (Box 17-3)
    - Northeast Utilities-Proposed Transmission Line (Box 17-3)
    - Vehicles (Box 17-3)
    - CT State Soil Conservation Advisory Committee (Box 17-4)
    - Move Plan (Return of Requested Information on Personnel and Equipment Requirements) (Box 17-4)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 17-4)
    - Connecticut Valley Urban Area Project (Box 17-4)
    - O (Box 17-4)
    - Oil Spills (Box 17-4)
    - P (Box 17-4)
    - Parking Facilities-Route 86 Tolland and Willington (Box 17-4)
    - State Park (Box 17-4)
    - Pollution-Thames River (Norwich) (Box 17-4)
    - Power Facility Evaluation Council (Box 17-4)
    - Preservation and Conservation (Box 17-4)
    - R (Box 17-4)
    - Regulations (Box 17-4)
    - Radio Communications (Box 17-4)
    - Recycling (Box 17-4)
    - S (Box 17-4)
    - Small Business Administration (Box 17-4)
    - Secretary of the State’s Office (Box 17-4)
    - Snowmobiles (Box 17-4)
    - Soil and Water Conservation (Box 17-4)
    - Solid Waste (Compliance) (Box 17-4)
    - Solid Waste-News Publication (Box 17-4)
    - Solid Waste Publications and Brochures (Box 17-4)
    - Solid Waste, Wakeman/Walworth (Box 17-4)
- Series 12. Office of General Counsel, 1973-1974; 1988-027 (part)
  Box 24-1 also contains material for Series 11, Planning and Standards.
  - State of CT vs. Alwin Construction Co., Inc. Volume 1 (Box 24-1)
  - State of CT vs. Alwin Construction Co., Inc. Volume 2 (Box 24-1)
  - State of CT vs. Alwin Construction Co., Inc. Volume 3 (Box 24-1)
  - Candlewood Lake Hearings (Box 24-1)
  - Grounding of F.L. Hayes, Volume 1 (Box 24-1)
  - Grounding of F.L. Hayes, Volume 2 (Box 24-1)
  - State of CT vs. Steven Weil et. al. (Box 24-1)
  - Candlewood Lake, Steven Weil Hearings (Box 24-1)
- Series 13. Interagency Files, 1973; 1988-027 (part)
  - Public Utilities Commission, 1973
    - CT Light and Power Co., Application for Increases in Electric and Gas Rates, Docket No. 11399, 1973 April (Box 25-1)
    - Hartford Electric Light Co., Application for Increases in Electric and Gas Rates, Docket No. 11400, 1973 April (Box 25-1)
    - Encroachment-General (Box 25-1)
    - PUC Hearings, 1973 (Box 25-1)
    - Additional Testimony of R.S. Bromage (Box 25-1)
    - Exhibits, G-43 to ML-Z (Box 25-1)
    - Brief of the Hartford Electric Light Co., Docket No. 11400 (Box 25-1)
    - Brief for Intervener CCAG, Docket No. 11400 (Box 25-1)
    - 10 and 20 year Forecasts of Loads and Resources (Box 25-1)
    - Brief for Intervener, Berkshire-Litchfield Environmental Council, Docket 11390 (Box 25-1)
    - Testimony and Exhibits (Box 25-1)
    - Reply Brief to the City of Hartford (Box 25-1)
- Series 19. Office of Communications and Education, 1972-1998
  - Director, 1972-1998
    - Subject Files, 1972-1998; 1998-035
      - Acid rain (Box 1)
      - Adjudications (Box 1)
      - Anniversary (Founder's Day) (Box 1)
      - BES organization (Box 1)
      - BES organization, 1989-1990 (Box 1)
      - BES organization (Box 1)
      - Boating safety education (Box 1)
      - Bottle Bill, 4 folders (Box 1)
      - Bottle Bill, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
      - Bottle Bill correspondence, circa 1980-1989 (Box 1)
      - Bottle Bill hearings, circa 1980-1989 (Box 1)
      - Bottle Bill inquiries, 1981-1986, 1995 (Box 1)
      - Bottle Bill - Laws - Press Releases, 1980 (Box 1)
      - Bottle Bill - Proposed Changes (Box 1)
      - Boating (Box 1)
      - Budget / cut backs (Box 1)
      - Bureau of Fisheries - 1986 Federal Assistance Program (Box 1)
      - Careers (Box 1)
      - CCC Reunion (Box 1)
      - Citizen's Advisory Board for Non-harvested Wildlife, 1992 (Box 1)
      - Citizen's Advisory Council, 1995 (Box 1)
      - Civil penalty - Bottle Bill (Box 1)
      - Clerical support (Box 1)
      - Coastal creatures (Box 1)
      - Commissioner speech, 1991 (Box 1)
      - Conn. Env. (Box 1)
      - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1972-1983 (Box 1)
      - Correspondence / speeches (Box 1)
      - CT Native Americans (Box 1)
      - Customer Service Committees Directory (Box 1)
      - DEP accomplishments, 1991 (Box 1)
      - DEP Advisory Council - ByLaws, 1987 (Box 1)
      - DEP Affirmative Action (Box 1)
      - DEP 25th Anniversary (Box 1)
      - DEP logo (Box 1)
      - DEP organization / info / education programs (Box 1)
      - DEP slogan (Box 1)
      - DEP Web Site Committee (Box 1)
      - Deposit law (Box 1)
      - Division correspondence (Box 1)
      - Education - Branch of Env. Conv. (Box 1)
      - Education Committee (Box 1)
      - Education Committee (Box 2)
      - Education materials (Box 2)
      - Emergency regulation - extension (Box 2)
      - Education - current (Box 2)
      - Education - forestry related (Box 2)
      - Enforcement EQ (Box 2)
      - Environmental Quality (Box 2)
      - Environmental Exchange (Box 2)
      - Environmental Industries (Box 2)
      - Fairs (Box 2)
      - Fiscal (Box 2)
      - Gen. Admin. (Box 2)
      - General info (Box 2)
      - Goodwin Conservation Center (Box 2)
      - Grants (Box 2)
      - Heritage CT (Box 2)
      - Historical (Box 2)
      - I & E Office Procedures (Box 2)
      - Impact of Bottle Bill, 1980 (Box 2)
      - Inside Out (Box 2)
      - I. T. Committee (Box 2)
      - Keeney testimony (Box 2)
      - Land conservation (Box 2)
      - Leg. (Box 2)
      - Legal clinic (Box 2)
      - LIS displays (Box 2)
      - LIS fund applications (Box 2)
      - LIS grants (Box 2)
      - Litter survey, 1980 (Box 2)
      - Management (Box 2)
      - Manager's meeting, 1985 March 28 (Box 2)
      - Maps misc. (Box 2)
      - Maps - publications store construction (Box 2)
      - Mapping Committee (Box 2)
      - Misc. current (Box 2)
      - Northeast Fish & Wildlife (NEFW) Conference (Box 2)
      - Needs survey - publications (Box 2)
      - Newsletter, Magazine, Inside Out (Box 2)
      - Notification - regulation - making proceed. (Box 2)
      - NRCE Committee (Box 2)
      - Official statements (Box 2)
      - OEE (Box 2)
      - Oil recycling (Box 2)
      - PCB (Box 2)
      - Pesticides (Box 2)
      - Press releases - Air (Box 2)
      - Publications (Margot) (Box 2)
      - PSAs (Box 2)
      - Publication reductions (Box 2)
      - Publication responsibilities (Box 2)
      - Purchasing Review Committee (Box 2)
      - Sight & Sound - Special Olympics (Box 2)
      - Special events (Box 2)
      - Special Olympics (Box 3)
      - Sportsmen's Clubs, 1973-1975 (Box 3)
      - Strategic Plan draft (Communications / Ed), 1995-1997 (Box 3)
      - Take Pride in America (Box 3)
      - TERC Update, 1991 February (Box 3)
      - TIP law enf. (Box 3)
      - Urban & community ecology initiative (Box 3)
      - Urban ed. / career dev. (Box 3)
      - USDA Forest Service / Nat. Res. Cons. Ed. Grants (Box 3)
      - Volunteers - reports, 1989 (Box 3)
      - Water abatement programs, 1972 (Box 3)
      - Water information (Box 3)
      - WET grants (Box 3)
      - WILD (Box 3)
      - Testimony in support of an increased handling fee paid to dealers or operators of redemption centers (presented by CT Food Stores Assoc.), circa 1981 (Box 3)
      - Env. Prot. - teletape information services (Box 3)
      - Litter control statutes/regulations (Box 3)
      - DEP - budget request, 1974-1975 (Box 3)
      - DEP lake & pond surveys, envelope (Box 3)
      - DEP rules of practice, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Subject Files, 1992-1993; 1998-036 (part)
      - DEP Senior staff meeting (Box 1)
      - Senior staff meeting, 1993 January - May (Box 1)
      - Senior staff meeting, 1993; 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Early retirement, 1992 (Box 1)
      - Sidney J. Holbrook meeting (Box 1)
    - Sound recordings, 1972-1996; 1998-039 (Box Envelope)
      - Bottle Bill hearing, 1987 April 10; 2 audio cassettes
      - Citizen's Advisory Council meeting, 1996 May 14; 1 audio cassette
      - "Connecticut's Mandatory Deposit Law", Public service announcement, 1 audio cassette
      - Panel discussion by Conservation Commissioners, 1972 July 27; 1 reel
      - Unidentified reel from DEP Information/Publications
  - Deputy Press Secretary, 1991
    - Office Files - Gov. Weicker, 1991; 1998-036 (part)
      - Avice (Box 1)
      - Daily updates - Weicker's ofifce (Box 1)
      - Emergency Plan II, 1991 August 1 (Box 1)
      - Staffing (Box 1)
- Series 20. Office of Affirmative Action, 1977-1996; 2001-017
  - Affirmative Action Advisory Council administrative files, 1977-1996
    - Organization charts, circa 1987-1996 (Box 1)
    - Organizational evaluation recommendations draft and final report, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Memos, 1977-1984 (Box 1)
    - Minutes, 1978-1984 (Box 1)
    - Material, 1985 (Box 1)
    - CHRO correspondence, 1987 (Box 1)
    - Meeting announcement, appointments, 1987-1989 (Box 1)
    - Minutes, agendas, appointments, communications, member list, bylaws, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Minutes, agendas, annual reports, mission statement, 1991-1992 (Box 1)
    - Minutes, agendas, communications, 1991-1992 (Box 1)
    - Minutes, agendas, meeting announcements, background material, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Quarterly report, 1993 (Box 1)
    - 1993-1996 (Box 1)
    - Handwritten notes, 1992-1995 (Box 1)
    - Program Coordinator report, minutes, agenda, appointments, memos, 1986 (Box 1)
- Series 21. Human Resources, 1944-1974; 2007-044
  - Seasonal History Cards, 1944-1969
    Restricted.
    - A-N, 1954-1957 (Box 1)
    - O-Z, 1954-1957 (Box 2)
    - A-Z, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Pi-Z, 1949-1954 (Box 3)
    - A-M, 1944-1948 (Box 3)
    - N-Z, 1944-1948 (Box 4)
    - A-C, 1944 (Box 4)
    - D-Mar, 1944 (Box 5)
    - Mas-Z, 1944 (Box 6)
    - A-R, 1959-1962 (Box 7)
    - S-Z, 1969-1962 (Box 8)
    - Misc., 1960-1969 (Box 7)
    - A-Cf, 1963-1969 (Box 8)
    - Ch-Lav, 1963-1969 (Box 9)
    - Lay-V, 1963-1969 (Box 10)
    - A-Z, 1965 (Box 11)
  - Employee History Cards, A-Z, 1969-1974 (Box 12)